Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records WAG.281
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Networks
  - ABC: Agreements- Sustaining Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1954-1956 (Box 110, Folder 55)
  - ABC: Agreements- [National] Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1956-1958, 1957 (Box 110, Folder 56)
  - ABC: Agreements- [National] Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1958-1960 (Box 110, Folder 57)
  - ABC: Agreements- [National] Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1960-1963, 1961 (Box 110, Folder 58)
  - ABC: Agreements- [National] Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 59)
  - ABC: Agreements- [National] Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1966-1969 (signed), 1968 (Box 110, Folder 60)
  - ABC: Agreement- WGBH- Boston, 1973-1974 (Box 110, Folder 61)
  - ABC: Agreement with Scott Muni, 1960 (Box 110, Folder 62)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFRA vs ABC re: Announcing Staff, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 63)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFRA vs ABC on behalf of Walter McDonough, 1948 (Box 110, Folder 64)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs ABC re: Cancellation of Jerry Lewis Show due to JFK Assassination, 1963-1964 (Box 110, Folder 65)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs ABC re: "Cancelled Programs" and "Cancelled Individual Engagements", 1961-1962 (Box 110, Folder 66)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs ABC re: Discharge of Wallace C Bruner, 1966-1967 (Box 110, Folder 67)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs ABC re: Discharged Announcers, 1955-1957 (Box 110, Folder 68)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs ABC re: Gypsy Rose Lee Program, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 69)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA (NY) vs ABC re: Newsmen Claims for [JFK] Assassination Weekend, 1964-1965 (Box 110, Folder 70)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA (NY) vs ABC re: Promos and Stand-Bys, 1964-1965 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA (NY) vs ABC re: Staff Newsmen Representation, 1964-1965 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA (NY) vs ABC re: Staff Newsmen Representation- AFTRA and ABC Briefs, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA (NY) v. ABC re: "Swan Lake - Minnesota", 1984-1985 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFRA vs Blue Network Co. re: "True Story Theatre of the Air", 1942-1943 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA for member Darla Hood v. ABC, 1958-1959 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- Bond, Ford v. Blue Network, Inc., 1942 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- Commercial Fees to Staff Announcers "Galen Drake" Program, 1948 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- DeMille, Agnes v. WABC, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- Kaufman, Murray A./Belplaza Corp. v. ABC, 1953-1954 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- Logging Duties at WABC Radio, 1962 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- McNeil, Don vs ABC re: Pension and Welfare Contributions, 1959 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- Sheldon, Herb vs ABC, 1952 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- Starr, Martin vs ABC, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - ABC: Claims and Arbitrations- White, Lawrence vs Henry Morgan (Withdrawn), 1945-1946 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1950-1952 (signed), 1951 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1952-1954 (signed), 1953 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1954-1956 (signed), 1953-1954 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1956-1958 (signed), 1957 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1960-1963 (signed), 1961 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1963-1966 (signed), 1964 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1966-1969 (signed), 1968 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1969-1972 (signed), 1970 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio, Los Angeles and West Coast for 1963-1966 (signed), 1964 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio, Pacific Coast Regional for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - ABC: Codes- Commercial Radio, Pacific Coast Regional for 1960-1963 (signed), 1961 (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - ABC: Codes- Memorandum of Changes, 1953 (Box 111, Folder 28)
  - ABC: Codes- Television Authority (TVA) for 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 29)
  - ABC: Codes- [Network] Television Broadcasting for 1952-1954 (signed), 1953 (Box 111, Folder 30)
  - ABC: Codes- [Network] Television Broadcasting for 1954-1956 (signed) (Box 111, Folder 31)
  - ABC: Codes- [Network] Television Broadcasting for 1956-1958 (signed), 1957 (Box 111, Folder 32)
  - ABC: Codes- [Network] Television Broadcasting for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 111, Folder 33)
  - ABC: Codes- [Network] Television Broadcasting for 1960-1963 (signed), 1961 (Box 111, Folder 34)
  - ABC: Codes- [Network] Television Broadcasting for 1963-1966 (signed) (Box 111, Folder 35)
  - ABC: Codes- [Network] Television Broadcasting for 1966-1969 (signed), 1967 (Box 111, Folder 36)
  - ABC: Codes- [Network] Television Broadcasting for 1969-1972, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 37)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Chicago for 1952-1954 (signed), 1953 (Box 111, Folder 38)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Chicago for 1954-1956 (signed), 1955 (Box 111, Folder 39)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Chicago for 1956-1958 (signed) (Box 111, Folder 40)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Chicago for 1963-1966 (signed), 1965 (Box 111, Folder 41)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Chicago for 1966-1969 (signed), 1968 (Box 111, Folder 42)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Chicago for 1969-1972 (signed), 1971 (Box 111, Folder 43)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1952-1954 (signed) (Box 111, Folder 44)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1954-1956 (signed), 1955 (Box 111, Folder 45)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1956-1958 (signed), 1957 (Box 111, Folder 46)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 111, Folder 47)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1960-1963 (signed), 1961 (Box 111, Folder 48)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1963-1966 (signed), 1964 (Box 111, Folder 49)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1966-1969 (signed), 1968 (Box 111, Folder 50)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1969-1972 (signed), 1970 (Box 111, Folder 51)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, Los Angeles for 1973-1976 (signed), 1975 (Box 111, Folder 52)
  - ABC: Codes- Television Recorded Commercials for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 111, Folder 53)
  - ABC: Codes- Television Recorded Commercials for 1960-1963 (signed), 1961 (Box 111, Folder 54)
  - ABC: Codes- Television Recorded Commercials for 1963-1966 (signed), 1964 (Box 111, Folder 55)
  - ABC: Codes- Television Recorded Commercials for 1966-1969 (signed), 1967 (Box 111, Folder 56)
  - ABC: Codes- Television Recorded Commercials for 1969-1972 (signed), 1971 (Box 111, Folder 57)
  - ABC: Codes- Television, San Francisco for 1971-1974 (Box 111, Folder 58)
  - ABC: Codes- Transcriptions [and Recordings] for Radio for 1950-1952 and 1952-1954 (signed), 1951-1954 (Box 111, Folder 59)
  - ABC: Codes- Transcriptions for 1956-1958 (signed), 1957 (Box 111, Folder 60)
  - ABC: Codes- Transcriptions for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 111, Folder 61)
  - ABC: Codes- Transcriptions for 1960-1963 (signed), 1961 (Box 111, Folder 62)
  - ABC: Codes- Transcriptions for 1963-1966 (signed), 1964 (Box 111, Folder 63)
  - ABC: Codes- Transcriptions for 1966-1969 (signed), 1968 (Box 111, Folder 64)
  - ABC: Codes- Transcriptions for 1969-1972 (signed), 1970 (Box 111, Folder 65)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1954-1956 (signed) (Box 111, Folder 66)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1956-1958 (Box 111, Folder 67)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1958-1960 (Box 111, Folder 68)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1960-1963, 1961 (Box 111, Folder 69)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 70)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1966-1969, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 71)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1973-1976, 1974 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in Los Angeles for 1982-1985, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - ABC: Contracts- Staff Announcers in New York for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1945-1948 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1953-1959 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1964-1966, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - ABC: Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - ABC: Correspondence (from Becker, Mortimer), 1959-1960 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - ABC: Correspondence re: Beutel, Bill Contract, 1962 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - ABC: Correspondence re: Block, Martin Show, 1954, 1959 (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - ABC: Correspondence re: Commercial Religious Radio Programs, 1959-1961 (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - ABC: Correspondence (from Conaway, Donald), 1956-1962 (Box 112, Folder 27)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Eismann, Bernard Discharge/Termination of Employment, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 28)
  - ABC: Correspondence re: "Fashions on Trial", 1953-1957 (Box 112, Folder 29)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Fels, Jerome re: Federal Communication Commission/Acree, 1945 (Box 112, Folder 30)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1949-1952 (Box 112, Folder 31)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1953-1954 (Box 112, Folder 32)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1955-1956 (Box 112, Folder 33)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1957 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1958 (Box 112, Folder 35)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1959 (Box 112, Folder 36)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 37)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1961-1962 (Box 112, Folder 38)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1963-1964 (Box 112, Folder 39)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Groot, Kenneth, 1965-1966, 1981-1982 (Box 112, Folder 40)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Heller, George, 1942-1947 (Box 112, Folder 41)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Heller, George, 1948-1955 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Hoffman, Harold, 1949-1953 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Howe, Quincy re: Pension, 1958-1959 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - ABC: Correspondence, "Joe Franklin's Memory Lane", 1960 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Jones, Raymond, 1956 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Lewis, Irving, 1955-1958 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Lewis, Irving, 1959-1963 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - ABC: Correspondence, McKee, Alex, 1951-1955 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Network News Audit, 1988-1989 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - ABC: Correspondence, "Nairobi Trio" on Ernie Kovacs Special, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Pension and Welfare Payments, 1957-1962 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Pre-Recorded Network Identification, 1957-1958 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - ABC: Correspondence, "Queen for a Day", 1960-1961 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Reel, Frank, 1950-1953 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Riggs, Glenn Contract, 1966 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - ABC: Correspondence, Staff Announcer Negotiations, 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - ABC: Correspondence, "Video Venus," MacLevy Video Productions, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - ABC: Grievances, 1961-1964 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - ABC: Grievances, 1965-1966 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - ABC: Grievances re: Coop Programming, 1950-1955 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - ABC: "Jack's Place," The Jerry Lester Show, 1953-1954 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - ABC: Loan-Out Material for Contract Players, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - ABC: News Severance Disputes, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - ABC: Silver Anniversary Special, Artist Agreement, 1977-1978 (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - ABC: Silver Anniversary Special, Clip Usage Waivers, Oct 1977 - Nov 1977 (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - ABC: Silver Anniversary Special, Clip Usage Waivers, Dec 1977 - Jan 1978 (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - ABC: Silver Anniversary Special, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - ABC: Staff Announcers, Promotional Announcements, 1964-1968 (Box 113, Folder 28)
  - ABC: Stock Investment Plan, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 29)
  - ABC: "Television News: Who Decides What You'll See?", 1974 (Box 113, Folder 30)
  - ABC: Wage Rate Adjustment, National War Labor Board Form (signed by G. Heller) and March 1945 Agreement Copy (Box 113, Folder 31)
  - ABC: Waivers, 1953-1959 (Box 113, Folder 32)
  - ABC: Waivers, 1960-1970 (Box 113, Folder 33)
  - ABC: Waivers, "Flair", 1960-1961 (Box 113, Folder 34)
  - ABC: Waivers, Network Radio Post-Midnight, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 35)
  - ABC: Washington Correspondents' Work Schedules, Oct 1985 (Box 113, Folder 36)
  - ABC: Washington Correspondents' Work Schedules, Nov 1985 (Box 113, Folder 37)
  - ABC: Washington Correspondents' Work Schedules, Dec 1985 (Box 113, Folder 38)
  - ABC: Washington Correspondents' Work Schedules, Jan 1986 (Box 113, Folder 39)
  - ABC: Washington Correspondents' Work Schedules, Feb 1986 (Box 113, Folder 40)
  - ABC: Washington Correspondents' Work Schedules, Mar 1986 - Jun 1986 (Box 113, Folder 41)
  - CBS: Agreements- AFRA and CBS Assignment of Agreement, 1940 (Box 113, Folder 42)
  - CBS: Agreements- American Federation of Musicians, Chicago for 1937-1940 (signed) (Box 113, Folder 43)
  - CBS: Agreements- American Guild of Radio Announcers and Producers, WABC Chapter, 1939-1940 (Box 113, Folder 44)
  - CBS: Agreement- AM Local Staff Directors, New York for 1959-1960 (Box 113, Folder 45)
  - CBS: Agreements- Assistant Directors for 1939-1942 (signed), 1940 (Box 113, Folder 46)
  - CBS: Agreements- Assistant Directors [and Announcers] (signed), 1942 (Box 113, Folder 47)
  - CBS: Agreements- Assistant Directors (signed), 1943 (Box 113, Folder 48)
  - CBS: Agreements- Assistant Directors (signed), 1944 (Box 113, Folder 49)
  - CBS: Agreements- CBS, Musicians Local 10 and AFM, Chicago, 1937-1939 (Box 113, Folder 50)
  - CBS: Agreements- Commercial Radio Programs, Chicago (signed), 1951 (Box 113, Folder 51)
  - CBS: Agreements- Commercial Radio Broadcasting, West Coast for 1941-1943 (signed), 1940 (Box 113, Folder 52)
  - CBS: Agreements- Free Lance Singers for 1948-1949 (Box 113, Folder 53)
  - CBS: Agreements- IBEW Jurisdiction (signed), 1947 (Box 113, Folder 54)
  - CBS: Agreements- IBEW, 1943 (Box 113, Folder 55)
  - CBS: Agreements- Memorandum Agreement, Chicago for 1948-1950 (signed) (Box 113, Folder 56)
  - CBS: Agreements- Memorandum Agreement, West Coast for 1948-1950 (signed) (Box 113, Folder 57)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sound Effects Men, Chicago for 1940 and Amended (signed), 1943 (Box 113, Folder 58)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sound Effects Men, Chicago for 1944 (signed) (Box 113, Folder 59)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sound Effects Men, Chicago for 1948-1950 (signed) (Box 113, Folder 60)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sound Effects Men, Chicago for 1952-1954 (signed), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 61)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sound Effects Men, Chicago for 1954-1956 (signed), 1955 (Box 113, Folder 62)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sound Effects Men, Chicago for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 113, Folder 63)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sound Effects Men, New York, 1939 (Box 113, Folder 64)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sound Effects Men, New York for 1944-1946 (signed) with Related Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 113, Folder 65)
  - CBS: Agreements- [Short-Wave] Staff Announcer-Producers for 1945-1946 (signed) (Box 113, Folder 66)
  - CBS: Agreements- [Short-Wave] Staff Announcer-Producers for 1946-1948 (signed), 1947-1948 (Box 113, Folder 67)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers for 1948-1950 (signed) (Box 113, Folder 68)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers for 1950-1952 (signed), 1951 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Chicago for 1940-1943 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Chicago for 1952-1954 (signed), 1953 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Chicago for 1954-1956 (signed), 1955 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Chicago for 1956-1957 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Chicago for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Chicago for 1963-1966 (signed), 1964 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Chicago for 1966-1969 (signed), 1968 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Los Angeles for 1952-1954 (signed), 1953 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Los Angeles for 1956-1958 (signed), 1957 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Los Angeles for 1958-1960 (signed), 1959 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, Los Angeles for 1985-1988 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1942-1944 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York, 1944 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1946-1948, 1947 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1948-1950 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1952-1954, 1953 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1954-1956, 1955 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1956-1958 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1958-1960 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1960-1963, undated (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Announcers, New York for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen for 1966-1969 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen for 1973-1976 (signed), 1973-1975 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen for 1976-1979, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newspersons for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newspersons for 1982-1985 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen, Chicago for 1966-1969, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen, Los Angeles for 1966-1969 (signed), 1968 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newspersons, Los Angeles for 1973-1976 (signed), 1974 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newspersons, Los Angeles for 1976-1979 (signed), 1977 (Box 114, Folder 33)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newspersons, Los Angeles for 1979-1982 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newspersons, Los Angeles for 1982-1985, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen, New York for 1966-1969, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen, New York for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen, New York for 1973-1976, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 38)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen, New York for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 114, Folder 39)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newsmen, New York for 1979-1982 (Box 114, Folder 40)
  - CBS: Agreements- Staff Newspersons, New York for 1982-1985 (Box 114, Folder 41)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining Agreement for Actors and Singers (signed), 1938 (Box 114, Folder 42)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1940-1943 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 43)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1943-1944 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 44)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1944-1946 (Box 114, Folder 45)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1952-1954 (signed), 1953 (Box 114, Folder 46)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1954-1956 (signed), 1955 (Box 114, Folder 47)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1956-1958 (signed), 1957 (Box 114, Folder 48)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1958-1960 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 49)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1960-1963 (signed), 1961 (Box 114, Folder 50)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for Actors and Singers for 1963-1966 (signed), 1964 (Box 114, Folder 51)
  - CBS: Agreements- Sustaining [Radio] Agreement for 1966-1969 (signed), 1968 (Box 114, Folder 52)
  - CBS: Agreements- Washington, DC for 1970-1973, 1971 (Box 114, Folder 53)
  - CBS: Benefit Plans, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 54)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFRA vs CBS re: "Choir Practice", 1947 (Box 114, Folder 55)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs CBS re: 5-Minute Local News Rate, 1961-1962, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 56)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs CBS re: Late Payment Penalty, Stan Freberg Spots, 1967 (Box 114, Folder 57)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs CBS re: "Stringers", 1981 (Box 114, Folder 58)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs Himan Brown re: "CBS Mystery Theatre," Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973-1979 (Box 114, Folder 59)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA vs Himan Brown re: "CBS Mystery Theatre," P&W Remittance Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 114, Folder 60)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA/New York Local/CBS/Newsmen, 1962-1964 (Box 114, Folder 61)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA/New York Local/John Douglas McLean Unemployment Insurance, 1960-1961 (Box 114, Folder 62)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- AFTRA/New York Local/John Douglas McLean Unemployment Insurance, 1962-1965 (Box 114, Folder 63)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- CBS vs AFRA re: Julliard School of Music, 1947-1949 (Box 114, Folder 64)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- CBS vs Motion Picture Home Office Employees Union/Radio Guild/Radio Broadcast Engineers, 1945-1946 (Box 114, Folder 65)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- In the Matter of Dino Narizzano, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 66)
  - CBS: Claims and Arbitrations- McNulty, Arthur P.V. CBS, 1960-1961 (Box 114, Folder 67)
  - CBS: Codes- Commercial Radio for 1939-1941 (signed) (Box 114, Folder 68)
  - CBS: Codes- Commercial Radio Broadcasting for 1941-1943, 1940 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - CBS: Codes- Commercial Radio Broadcasting for 1950-1952 (signed), 1951 (Box 115, Folder 2)